<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Work &amp; Projects on Jan van Iperen</title><link>https://janvaniperen.com/projects/</link><description>Recent content in Work &amp; Projects on Jan van Iperen</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://janvaniperen.com/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>indupro</title><link>https://janvaniperen.com/projects/indupro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://janvaniperen.com/projects/indupro/</guid><description>&lt;p>indupro connects people in the ingredients industry. Old-school networking and brokering skills meet technology and marketing leverage.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The company is owned and run by Jan van Iperen, a Dutch entrepreneur with 25 years of experience in the citrus, juice and beverage industry, who currently works and resides in California.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="history">History&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>indupro (industrial products) was established by Mr. John van Iperen, my late father. Continuing his experience working with his uncle August Dubru and after growing the export network for the Cutrale family since 1966, John initiates indupro as a trader/broker/agent firm in Rotterdam.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Juice News</title><link>https://janvaniperen.com/projects/juice-news/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://janvaniperen.com/projects/juice-news/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="overview">Overview&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Started in November 2014 with 22 recipients who received individually sent emails&amp;hellip; Juice News has grown to a newsletter with over 1600 recipients all over the world, and a website that is read by thousands every month.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>···&amp;gt; &lt;em>this post is being updated&lt;/em>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>MNML Hugo Theme</title><link>https://janvaniperen.com/projects/mnml-hugo-theme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://janvaniperen.com/projects/mnml-hugo-theme/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="overview">Overview&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>MNML is a minimalist Hugo theme designed for content creators who want a clean, distraction-free website. The theme focuses on typography and readability, ensuring that your content takes center stage.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="features">Features&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="clean-typography">Clean Typography&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>MNML uses a carefully selected typography system that prioritizes readability across different devices and screen sizes. The font choices and spacing are optimized for long-form reading.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="darklight-mode">Dark/Light Mode&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>The theme includes a toggle for dark and light modes, allowing readers to choose their preferred reading experience. The color scheme transitions smoothly between modes.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Sierra Agra USA</title><link>https://janvaniperen.com/projects/sierra-agra-usa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://janvaniperen.com/projects/sierra-agra-usa/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="company">Company&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Sierra Agra USA transforms the &amp;ldquo;unseen harvest&amp;rdquo;&lt;sup id="fnref:1">&lt;a href="#fn:1" class="footnote-ref" role="doc-noteref">1&lt;/a>&lt;/sup>—culled, rejected, or cosmetically imperfect produce—into a diverse portfolio of juices, purees, concentrates, and by-products, addressing a critical yet often overlooked issue in California&amp;rsquo;s Central Valley.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="roles">Roles&lt;/h2>
&lt;h3 id="advisor-to-the-board-marketing-consultant-july-2022--july-2024">Advisor to the Board, Marketing Consultant (July 2022 – July 2024)&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Drawing on my experience as a broker in the juice and beverage industry, I joined Sierra Agra USA in July 2022 as an advisor to the board, focusing on sales and marketing. I collaborated closely with the C-suite to shape the company’s positioning and marketing strategy, leveraging my industry network and expertise built through &lt;strong>indupro&lt;/strong> and my authority grown through &lt;strong>Juice News&lt;/strong> .&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>